reviso.com 2018-09-03

# Reviso.com - Privacy Policy

By using our websites, application, apps and surrounding services you accept this Privacy Policy and the collection of information as outlined in this Privacy policy.

## Why are we collecting personal information about you?

Reviso is an online accounting application. As part of registering for and using Reviso, you will be required to, or have the opportunity to, store information about companies, including your own, and people, including yourself.

The registration of Personal Information is required to provide access to the application, for billing and to provide the services surrounding the application. You may choose not to provide us with the required information, but it may result in us not being able to provide you with access to the application and services.

We also collect information about your use of the application and our websites that we use to provide you with support, and improve the application and services in the future.

We may make information available to courts of law or authorities if so required by local laws and regulations.

Finally we use your personal information to contact you with news about the application and the services and for marketing related communication towards you.

## Where do we collect information about you?

We collect personal information:

  * When you sign up for the application
  * Inside the application
  * In our Mobile Apps
  * When you visit our websites

## What data are we collecting?

### In our application and mobile apps:

When you sign up for the application we collect Personal Information about you in order to be able to verify your identity and bill you for the service. The information you register may include information that may be used to identify an individual (Personal Information), such as name, personal registration number, address, email, phone number etc. You may also register information about your company and third parties in the application.

When you report technical problems in the application, we may store Information related to the matter, and the resolution of the matter, that may identify you, inside the application or inside related services that we use to communicate with you on the matter.

We aggregate usage statistics and other non-personal information that does not identify you as a user, but may help us understand the performance and use of the application in order to further develop the application of services in the future.

### On our websites:

When you visit one of Reviso's websites, we automatically collect information about your visit. In other words, we monitor which pages you click on, if you've visited this website before as well as which other website or search engine you came from.

The information we collect from your visit cannot in any way be used to identify you personally. We use this information to monitor general tendencies in online user behaviour that may be used to improve the user experience on the websites in the future.

When you visit one or more of Reviso's websites, we may automatically collect the following data about your visit:

  * The page you entered first
  * Whether you have visited this website before
  * The duration of your visit
  * Which website or search engine you came from
  * The keyword(s) you entered in the search engine
  * Which web pages you visit
  * Your IP address
  * Your operating system as well as your browser type and version
  * Your screen resolution and the number of colours used by your PC
  * Whether your PC supports JavaScript and Flash
  * Language, country and zone/city

The data is collected using cookies, the so-called "web beacons" and log files. Most websites collect this type of information about their users, so this is a standard practice. You will be prompted to accept these cookies when you visit our websites for the first time.

## Third party personal information

When you register information in Reviso about third parties, e.g. suppliers or customers, it is your responsibility to obtain the required permission to do so beforehand. Reviso cannot be held liable for the legality of the information you enter in the application.

We will assist any party or court of law that contacts us, regarding registration of personal information that may be unlawful, in the investigation of the matter and if required by law or ordered by the court, we will disclose information to the court, and eventually change or delete information. You are required to assist us in such matters.

Please contact us at [help@reviso.com](mailto:help@reviso.com) for further help on the matter.

## Where do we store the data?

The Accounting data is stored on Microsoft Azure’s and Amazon’s servers in Ireland. A version of the German dataset is stored in a German data center. Deferred and secondary data may be stored with any of our service providers listed below.

We do not share your information with third parties without your consent other than the third party services that are required to provide our application and services to you. These include the following:

  * Amazon Web Services
  * Cloud AMQP
  * Compose.io
  * Google Analytics
  * Heroku
  * Hetzner
  * Intercom
  * Logentries
  * Mailchimp
  * Microsoft Azure
  * Mixpanel
  * And others

None of these third party services have access to your Personal Information. Your Personal Information is under our control at all times. If you do not want to have your Personal Information stored with any of the mentioned services, you should not provide us with the information, which in turn may mean that we cannot deliver our service to you.

All our US based service providers have signed the EU model clauses / privacy shield.

## Credit Cards

We do not store any credit card information. Online payments are processed by Stripe.

## Protection of personal information

You can find a description of the security measures behind the delivery of our services in this document: https://www.reviso.com/security

## Cookies

A cookie is a small file that is stored on your device by your web browser in order to recognise you. A Cookie is an open text file that interacts with the website in order to for instance store your preferences and provide analytics about your use of the site.

We use cookies as part of our application as well as the use of our website as described in this document. You may deny the acceptance of cookies or delete them, but this may affect your use of our service.

## Emails

The email address you enter when you sign up for the Reviso news mail is only used to send you emails regarding the application and services and the occasional news mails about new features and changes to the services.

You can cancel your subscription to the news mails by following the link at the bottom of the email. If you cancel your subscription to the news mail, we will retain your email address to ensure that you will no longer receive news mails from us.

## Changes to Personal Information

Please help keep your Personal Information up to date. If you are in doubt about what information we have stored about you and where, please contact us via our normal means of communications and get assistance.

## Contacting us

Questions related to this Privacy Policy or any other matter should be sent to us via our standard means of contact, which means either through email, the chat function on our website or in the Application, or by calling us.

## Right to update

Reviso may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. The current version of the Privacy Policy in force from time to time will be available on Reviso's website. Reviso shall endeavour to provide reasonable notice of any changes by posting such changes on the website in advance. Further use of the Application after any change to the Privacy Policy shall be deemed to be acceptance of such Policy. It is the Customer’s responsibility to check the website regularly to keep updated on any changes to this Policy.

Last updated: March 15, 2017
